ARNOLD PHILIP GOODWIN

CONTACT



Kolkata,India



+91 7278474560



arvinarnold96@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arnold-goodwin-68b2ab2

SOFTWARE

- Google Suite
- Slack
- Notion
- Freshdesk
- Chargebee
- Ameyo

SKILLS

- Customer service and support.
- Customer relations and communication.
- Complaint resolution.
- Creative problem solving.
- Presentation skills.
- Technical support and troubleshooting.
- Flexibility.
- Decision making.
- Fast learner.
- Emotional Intelligence.
- Critical Thinking Skills.
- Creativity.

HOBBIES

- Travelling and exploring.
- Playing football.
- Listening to music.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Seeking a position to utilize my skills and abilities in the industry, a job where growth prospects are unlimited and individuality is recognised by work, and to achieve professional satisfaction by meeting higher responsibilities and involving in competent work access.

LANGUAGES:

- English.
- Hinid.
- Bengali.

Customer Service Representative bringing top-notch skills in oral and written communication, active listening and analytical problemsolving skills. Enhance customer experiences by employing service oriented behaviors, understanding customer desires and providing customized solutions to build loyalty. Dedicated Customer Service professional having a successful track record of understanding client needs and providing quick resolution.

EXPERIENCE

September 2021 to Current

Customer Support Specialist REMO, Kolkata, India

- Provided primary customer support to internal and external customers in fast-paced manner.
- Patiently walked individuals through basic troubleshooting tasks.
- Identified bugs in clients events and shared it with the engineering team to find a quick fix.
- Supported customers throughout their event and delivered expert assistance for technical needs.
- Compiled customer feedback and recommended service delivery.
- Used company troubleshooting resolutions to evaluate technical problems while leveraging Personal expertise to find appropriate solutions.

September 2020 to September 2021

Customer Support Associate Amazon, Kolkata, India

- Answered product and service questions, suggesting other offerings to attract potential customers.
- Answered customer telephone calls promptly to avoid on-hold wait times.
- Responded to customer requests for products, services and company information.
- Answered questions regarding seller inventory, shipping, payments and buyer complaints.

April 2019 to September 2020

Senior Customer Service Executive Kochar Tech, Kolkata, India

- Provided excellent customer service by efficiently resolving issues and responding to inquiries.
- Listened to customers' questions and concerns to provide answers or responses.
- Handled multiple chats together, while maintain the AHT and CSAT.
- De-escalated irate customers and provided them resolution by understanding their situation and maintaining the company value.

EDUCATION

2020

Bachelors of Commerce- B.com (honours) International and Rural Marketing.

St. Xavier's College, Kolkata, India.

- Member of 'The Student's Council'.
- Elected Class Representative during the first four semesters (2017-19).
- Elected to General Manager (Hospitality) for 'XAVOTSAV' in 2018 and 2019.
- Represented College in several competitions.

2017

I.S.C Commerce

St. Mary's Orphanage and Day School., Kolkata, India.